🎵 나 같은 죄인 살리신 (찬송가 305장)
Amazing Grace (Hymn 305) - Arise Next Gen
[1절] 나 같은 죄인 살리신 주 은혜 놀라워
Amazing grace! how sweet the sound That saved a wretch like me!
잃었던 생명 찾았고 광명을 얻었네
I once was lost, but now am found, Was blind, but now I see.
[2절] 큰 죄악에서 건지신 주 은혜 고마워
'Twas grace that taught my heart to fear, And grace my fears relieved;
나 처음 믿은 그 시간 귀하고 귀하다
How precious did that grace appear The hour I first believed!
[3절] 이제껏 내가 산 것도 주님의 은혜라
Through many dangers, toils and snares, I have already come;
또 나를 장차 본향에 인도해 주시리
'Tis grace hath brought me safe thus far, And grace will lead me home.
[4절] 거기서 우리 영원히 주님의 은혜로
When we've been there ten thousand years, Bright shining as the sun,
해처럼 밝게 살면서 주 찬양 하리라
We've no less days to sing God's praise Than when we'd first begun.
🕊️ 주님의 은혜에 감사드립니다 · 아멘
Giving Thanks to God's Abundant Grace · Amen